A Guide to the Student Government Association Records, 1915-2015: UA 0007
Special Collections, Carrier Library, James Madison University
- Series 5: Meeting Minutes, 1929-2012
  - Minutes, 1982-1983 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Minutes, 1983-1984 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Minutes, 1984-1985 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Minutes, 1985-1986 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Minutes, 1986-1987 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Minutes, 1987-1988 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Minutes, 1989-1990 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Minutes, 1990-1991 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Minutes, 1991-1992 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Minutes, 1992-1993 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Minutes, 1993-1994 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Minutes, 1993-1994 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Minutes, 1994 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Minutes, 1995-1996 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Minutes, 1997-1998 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Senate Minutes, 2000 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Senate Minutes, 2000-2001 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Meeting Minutes Notes, 2001 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Senate Minutes, 2001 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Senate Minutes, 2001 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Executive Council Student Senate Minutes, 2001-2002 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Executive Council Student Senate Minutes, 2001-2002 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Student Senate Meeting Agendas, 2001-2002 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Student Senate Meeting Recording, December 3, 2002
    - Original VHS, December 3, 2002 (Box 30, Vhs UA0007-VHS-003)
  - SGA Senate Meeting Recording, NAACP February Review, January 21, 2003
    - Original VHS, tape 1, January 21, 2003 (Box 30, Vhs UA0007-VHS-001)
    - Original VHS, tape 2, January 21, 2003 (Box 30, Vhs UA0007-VHS-002)
  - Executive Minutes, 2004-2005 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - SGA Board of Visitors Meeting, 2011 (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - SGA Executive Board Meeting Agendas, 2011-2012 (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - Student Government Association Minutes, 2011-2012 (Box 15, Folder 7)
- Series 6: Legislative Files, 1989-2015
  This series contains a mixture of bills and resolutions from SGA's Student Senate, 1989-2012, with the bulk from the 1990s. The series contains a large amount of resolutions related to the organization's contingency fund through which SGA assists in providing funding to different student organization on campus. However, there are also several folders of various bills presented to the Student Senate including proposed legislation that address contemporary social issues such as sexual orientation, campus issues such as better toilet paper, and student issues such as students' rights to privacy.
  - Proposed Bills, 1989-1990 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Proposed Bills, 1990-1991 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Proposed Bills, 1991-1992 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Proposed Bills, 1992-1993 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Proposed Bills, 1993-1994 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Proposed Bills, 1994-1995 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Proposed Bills, 1996-1997 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Proposed Bills, 1997-1998 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Proposed Bills, 1998-1999 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Senate Bills, 1999-2000 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Bill Book, 2000 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Senate Bills, 2000 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Bill Book, 2000-2001 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Bill Book, 2000-2001 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Bill Book, 2000-2001 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Unnamed Binder, 2000-2001 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Hate Crimes, 2001 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Amendment Proxy Form, 2001-2002 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Student Senate Bills, 2001-2002 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Passed Constitutional Amendments, 2003 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Bills, 2002-2003 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Failed Constitutional Amendments, 2003 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Bills, 2004-2005 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Bills Killed in Committee, 2005-2006 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Bills Killed in Committee, 2005-2006 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Bills Killed in Committee, 2005-2006 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Gay, Lesbian, Bisexual, Transgendered (GLBT) Bill of Opinion, 2006 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - DeLock and DiDom's Binder of Bills, 2007-2008 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - DeLock and DiDom's Binder of Bills, 2007-2008 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Student Government Association Binder, 2008-2009 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Resolution, 2009-2010 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Contingency, 2009-2010 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Contingency, 2009-2012 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Bill of Opinion for American Sign Language Minor, 2011 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Resolutions, 2012 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Bills, 2012-2013 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Resolutions of 100th Senate, 2014-2015 (Box 19, Folder 8)
- Series 7: Financial Files, 1987-2014
  This series contains a variety of financial documents ranging from purchase orders and yearly budget information to travel receipts. A majority of the materials in this collection are budget reports providing financial information for different fiscal years. These reports are usually connected to the creation of the university's front-end budgets and often include budget information for other campus organizations such as the University Program Board, The Breeze, Black Student Alliance, and Student Ambassadors. A majority of the material removed from this series were: purchase orders; accounting and banking information; invoices; and receipts. This material was removed due to the presence of account information and social security numbers, and/or it was deemed that the material had little research value.
  - Miscellaneous Groups, 1987-1997 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Event Budgets, 1987-1998 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Internal Budgets, 1989-1990 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Internal Budgets, 1991-1995 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Budget Summaries and Financial Reports, 1994, 1997-1998 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Wheat First Reserve, 1994-1998 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Front End Budget, 1996-1998 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Executive Committee Trip to COSCO Convention, 1996, 1998-1999 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Ad Hoc Committee on Final Evaluation, 1998 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - SGA Book Sale, 1998 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Account Code 121200, Media Services SGA Budgetary Receipts FY, 1998-1999 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Account Code 1214000, Postal Service SGA Budgetary Receipts FY, 1998-1999 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Account Code 121800, Telecommunications SGA Budgetary Receipts FY, 1998-1999 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Class Council Budgets, 1998-1999 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Contingency, Reserve and other Club Accounts: SGA Budgetary Receipts FY, 1998-1999 (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Financial, 1998-1999 (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Financial Statements Monthly Fiscal Year, 1998-1999 (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - Front End Budgets, 1998-1999 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - SGA Budget, 1998-1999 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - SGA Budget, 1998-1999 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - SGA Budget, 1998-1999 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - SGA Handouts, Miscellaneous Fiscal year, 1998-1999 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Parris Papers, 1998-2000 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Account Code 122300, Registration Fees, 1999 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Front End Budget, Old, 1999 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Miscellaneous Revenue SGA Budgetary Receipts, 1999 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - SGA Budget, 1999 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Account Code 121800, Telecommunications, 1999-2000 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Contingency Account, 1999-2000 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Budget-Internal/Front End, 1999-2001 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Copier, 1999-2001 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Breeze Advertisements, 2000 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Financial, 2000 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Budgets, 2000-2001 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Contingency Criteria, 2000-2001 (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - SGA Budget, 2000-2002 (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Miscellaneous, 2001 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Murder Mystery Receipts, 2001 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - State Budget Information, 2001 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Account Code 121800, Telecommunications, 2001-2002 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Account Code 122100 Educational Training Workshops, 2001-2002 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Account Code 131100 Apparel Supplies, 2001-2002 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Account Code 131300 Stationary Forms, 2001-2002 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Account Code 137400 Education Supplies, 2001-2002 (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Account Code 153400 Copier Contract, 2001-2002 (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Account Code 221100 Peripheral Equipment, 2001-2002 (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Account Code 124600 Cash Transferred, 2001-2002 (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - Miscellaneous revenues, 2001-2002 (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - Recycled Paper Project, 2001-2002 (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - SGA Financial Files, 2001-2002 (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - SGA Financial Files, 2001-2002 (Box 23, Folder 15)
  - Ask Karen, 2001-2003 (Box 23, Folder 16)
  - Front End Budgeted Advisory Board, 2001, 2003-2006, 2008 (Box 23, Folder 17)
  - SGA Budget, 2002 (Box 23, Folder 18)
  - Account Code 121200 and 121400, 2002-2003 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Account Code 137700, Photo Supplies, 2002-2003 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Conference on Student Government Associations, 2002-2003 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Executive Board Agendas, 2002-2003 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Monthly Statements, 2002-2003 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Karen to Sign, 2003 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Retreat Funding, 2003 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Ordered Office Supplies, 2003-2004 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Supply Room Companies, 2003-2005 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Front End Advisory Board and SGA Finance Committee, 2008 (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - Front End Budget, 2010 (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - Karen Mercer, 2012 (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - Front End Budget FY 2014, 2013 (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - Contingency, 2013-2014 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Contingency, 2013-2014 (Box 25, Folder 2)
- Series 8: Disciplinary Reports, 1922-1973
  This series contains records of disciplinary hearings conducted by Student Council, 1922-1973. Examples of students' misconduct include smoking cigarettes, possession of smoking paraphernalia, riding with dates without proper permission, going downtown or off campus without proper permission, cheating on assignments and/or examinations, mild hazing, stealing books, shoplifting, and drinking. Punishments included warnings, being "campused," probation, and indefinite suspension.
  The Family Educational Rights and Privacy Act of 1974 (FERPA) mandates that certain disciplinary files in this series be restricted. FERPA protection ends with the death of the student. Therefore, records are opened for research 80 years after their creation when it is presumed that the student is deceased.
  - Student Council Minutes, 1922-1924 (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Student Council Minutes, 1925-1933 (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - Presidents Council Minutes and Juror Lists, 1923-1947 (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Disciplinary Reports, 1927 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Disciplinary Reports, January-June 1928 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Disciplinary Reports, October-December 1928 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Disciplinary Reports, 1929 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Disciplinary Reports, 1930 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Disciplinary Reports, 1931 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Disciplinary Reports, 1932 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Disciplinary Reports, 1933-1934 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Disciplinary Reports, 1935-1936 (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Disciplinary Reports, 1937-1939 (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - Disciplinary Reports - RESTRICTED, 1940 (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - Disciplinary Reports - RESTRICTED, 1941 (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - Disciplinary Reports - RESTRICTED, 1942-1943 (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - Disciplinary Reports - RESTRICTED, 1944-1945 (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - Disciplinary Reports - RESTRICTED, 1949-1952 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Disciplinary Reports - RESTRICTED, 1953 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Disciplinary Reports - RESTRICTED, 1954 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Disciplinary Reports - RESTRICTED, 1955 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Disciplinary Reports - RESTRICTED, 1956 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Disciplinary Reports - RESTRICTED, Summer 1956 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Disciplinary Reports - RESTRICTED, 1957 (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Disciplinary Reports - RESTRICTED, 1958 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Disciplinary Reports - RESTRICTED, 1958 (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Disciplinary Reports - RESTRICTED, 1959 (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Disciplinary Reports - RESTRICTED, 1960 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Disciplinary Reports - RESTRICTED, 1961 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Disciplinary Reports - RESTRICTED, 1962-1964 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Disciplinary Reports - RESTRICTED, 1965 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Disciplinary Reports - RESTRICTED, 1966 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Disciplinary Reports - RESTRICTED, 1967 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Disciplinary Reports - RESTRICTED, 1968 (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - Disciplinary Reports - RESTRICTED, 1969 (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - Disciplinary Reports - RESTRICTED, 1970 (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - Disciplinary Reports - RESTRICTED, 1971 (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - Disciplinary Reports - RESTRICTED, 1972 (Box 28, Folder 11)
- Series 9: Photographs, 2000-2014
  This series features five different groups of photographs, 2000-2014. The bulk of these photographs are connected to the SGA research of the Forrest Hill Riot in 2000; however, there are also photographs of the Class of 2009 Ring Premiere, the SGA Halloween Party, JMU's Big Event, and one of SGA's lobbying trips.
  - Forrest Hill Riot Research, 2000-2001 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Forrest Hill Riot Research, 2000-2001 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - SGA Halloween, 2004 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - SGA Halloween Reception, October 30, 2008 (Box 1, Cd-r UA0007-OP-002)
  - Ring Premiere Class of 2009, 2007 (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Ring Premiere Class of 2009, 2007 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - SGA Big Event, 2013, undated (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - SGA Group Photo on Canvas, 2015 (Box OV 2)
  - SGA Event Photographs, undated (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - Lobbying Trip, undated (Box 29, Folder 8)
- Series 10: Scrapbooks, 2001-2009
  This series contains material from eight different SGA scrapbooks dated 2001-2009. These scrapbooks have little descriptive text and mostly contain photographs of different SGA functions and events. These scrapbooks are some of the best representations of the SGA student experience, as the images in these book show the relationships and personalities of the individuals that comprise the organization. One of particular importance is the scrapbook containing the letters, pictures, and notes saved from the two-year anniversary memorial of 9-11. The SGA 2001-2002 scrapbook contains a photograph of SGA members with former Governor and Mayor Douglas Wilder and Senator Mark Warner.
  - SGA, 2001-2002 (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - 9-11 Cards and Letters, 2003 (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - SGA, 2003-2004 (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - Student Government Association, 2004-2005 (Box OV 1, Folder 1)
  - Student Government Association, 2005-2006 (Box OV 1, Folder 2)
  - SGA Be the Change, 2006-2007 (Box OV 1, Folder 3)
  - SGA, 2007-2008 (Box OV 1, Folder 4)
  - Student Government Association, 2008-2009 (Box OV 1, Folder 5)
- Series 11: Ephemera, 1930-2015
  This series contains a variety of realia related to the history of SGA, 1930-2014. There are several large gaps in this series; 1931-1954, 1970-1980, and 2002-2012. The ephemera in this collection primarily comprises shirts, posters, academic regalia, and installation programs; however, there are additional items such as an SGA travel mug and several plaques. "Mr. and Ms. Madison 2014" sashes are included.
  - Installation Ceremonies, 1930, 1955, 1957-1969 (Box 29, Folder 12)
  - Carrier Kutner Field Day Tournament Best Sportsmanship Award, undated (Box 29, Folder 13)
  - SGA Ephemera, undated (Box 29, Folder 14)
  - White COSGA Short-Sleeved T-Shirt, 2007 (Box OV 2)
  - White Madisonfest Long-Sleeve T-Shirt, with James Madison written on the Left-Chest, with silhouette of James Madison on the lower back, 2010 (Box OV 2)
  - White SGA Polo- with SGA logo on the left side of chest, undated (Box OV 2)
  - Red @SGAjmu T-Shirt: has different hashtag phrases on the front, undated (Box OV 2)
  - Green Class of 2013.5 T-Shirt- writing on the front pocket, undated (Box OV 2)
  - Red Class of 2013.5 T-Shirt- writing on the front pocket, undated (Box OV 2)
  - Purple SGA Lacrosse Penny- SGA written in white, bold letters on the front, undated (Box OV 2)
  - Gray SGA Polo- Student Government Association James Madison University embroidered on the left side of chest with purple logo, undated (Box OV 2)
  - Gray Big Event T-Shirt- purple writing with Wilson cupola, undated (Box OV 2)
  - Red I'm Nerdy and I Know it T-shirt- Black outline of pocket with eye-glasses, undated (Box OV 2)
  - Stainless steel SGA travel mug- SGA logo in purple, undated (Box OV 2)
  - Student Government Association 100 Year Anniversary Button, undated (Box OV 2)
  - Student Government Association Finance Team Calculator, undated (Box OV 2)
  - Purple Class of 2015 T-shirt- JMU seal on the front pocket, undated (Box OV 2)
  - Blue Class of 2015 T-shirt- JMU seal on the front pocket, undated (Box OV 2)
  - Gray Ring Premiere Class of 2017 T-shirt- logo on the front left, undated (Box OV 2)
  - Yellow Class of 2018 T-shirt – purple drawings places on campus, undated (Box OV 2)
  - White SGA graduation regalia, undated (Box OV 2)
  - Mr. Madison 2014 sash, 2014 (Box OV 2)
  - Ms. Madison 2014 sash, 2014 (Box OV 2)
  - SGA Posters, 2013-2014 (Box OV 3, Folder 1)
    - SGA Presents: Madison Fest, 2013
    - Class of 2015 Ring Premiere, 2013
    - Madison Week, 2013
    - Madison Fest, 2014
    - Class of 2017 Ring Collection Premiere, 2015
    - Class of 2014 Senior Bucket List, undated
    - Class of 2015 Senior Bucket List, undated
    - We Went to JMU When, undated
    - A Resolution to Harrisonburg/Rockingham Community, 2014
  - Student Government Association, Class Officer of the Year Plaque, 1995-2001 (Box OV 3, Folder 2)
  - James Madison University Homecoming: Most Spirited Award, 2004 (Box OV 3)
  - COSGA Participation Award, 2002 (Box OV 3)
  - Student Government Association: Outstanding Student at Large Plaque, 1983-2001 (Box OV 3)
  - Student Government Association: Outstanding Student Senator of the Year Plaque, 1980 (Box OV 3)